AARON HU

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Phone: 510-967-6063,

Email: <u>aaron1515@gmail.com</u>,

URL: Aaron-Hu.com,

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/aaron1515,

Github: https://github.com/Aaron1515, Location: [San Francisco, East Bay]

PROFILE

}

I decided to follow my passion and pursued the knowledge and experience necessary to be a successful engineer. Inquisitive about new technologies and open to ideas. Ability to make good technical decision to effectively push a project to completeness. In pursuit of opportunities and challenges that will advance my skills and career.

SKILLS

Exposure to: Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, Sintra, Git, API, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap **Exposure to:** MongoDB, Redis, Devise, Python, Node, Turn.js, Express, Scaling

METHODOLOGY

Agile Development, Version Control(Disaster Recovery), Deployment, Test-Driven Development

PROJECTS

Workout Tracker: Workout app for trainer's and their clients

Created Rails app and encrypted with 128bit encryption to allow safety of our users. Expanded knowledge by incorporating D3 for a graphic-user interface for progress of training. Designed a small but complex relational database with algorithms to query database easily.

Pirateme: Ruby Gem

Published: <u>rubygems.org/gems/Pirateme</u>

Over 162 downloads within the first hour and over 500 on the first day. Created a gem to seed database. Gem is open source for use for other developers to use add or contribute.

EXPERIENCE

DEV BOOTCAMP, SAN FRANCISCO, CA - 2015 - 2016

(AN INTENSIVE WEB-DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM)

Taught and mentored other students. Knowledgeable in relational and non relational database. Worked effectively as part of a team to achieve goals by participated in pair programing on projects. Spent over 1000 hours developing software in Ruby and JavaScript.

AT&T, OAKLAND, CA - 2010 - 2015

(B2B SALES / CONSUMER SALES LEAD)

Created long term relationships with clients.

Organizer for monthly meetings.

Ran morning meetings for sales team.

DEV BOOTCAMP, SAN FRANCISCO, CA - 2014 - 2010

(B2B SALES / GEEK SQUAD)

Awarded best in sales the every month.

Arranged work area to improve repair times by 30%.

Quickly promoted to lead repair and lead sales in both positions.

EDUCATION

LAS POSITAS, LIVERMORE, CA - 2012-2014

Average GPA 3.5 - Computer Science Major